As of right now, we have this as our optimization objective function.
目前这就是我们的优化目标函数
But there's one other term that it's a good idea to add to it at this point.
但是最好再添加另一项
This is what's called a regularization term.
称为正则化项
Here we use the L2 norm of the portfolio weights as the regularization term.
我们使用投资组合权重的 L2 范数作为正则化项
In other types of problems,
在其他类型的问题中
you might use a different term.
你也许会使用其他的正则化项
What this do? Well, as you'll recall,
L2 范数有什么作用？你可能还记得
the L2 norm of a vector is its length.
向量的 L2 范数是向量的长度
So, in this case, the term is basically the length of the vector of portfolio weights.
这一项就相当于投资组合权重向量的长度
This entire quantity will get very large if the weight on any single asset gets large.
如果任一单个资产的权重变得很大 整个这一项将变得很大
So, the effect is to penalize this behavior
作用就是限制这种行为
and enforce the spreading of weight amongst assets.
并强制将权重分散到各个资产上
The parameter here controls the balance between maximizing
这个参数可以控制最大化投资组合 alpha
the portfolio alpha and enforcing the spreading of the weights across assets.
与强制在各个资产上分散权重之间的平衡性
To further clarify this,
为了进一步阐明这一点
let's imagine two possible extreme states of the world.
假设有两个很极端的情形
In the first, you feel maximally confident in your alpha factors.
在第一种情形下 你对你的 alpha 因子非常有信心
You know for sure which stocks are going to go up and down in the future and by how much.
你完全知道哪些股票未来将上涨多少 哪些将下跌多少
In this situation you'd put all your long money in the stocks that will go
在这种情形下 你将所有做多的资金投入将上涨最多的股票上
up the most and all your short money in the stocks that will go down the most.
并将所有做空资金投入将下跌最多的股票上
In the second extreme state,
在第二种极端情形下
you are absolutely sure that you know which
你完全确定你知道
stocks are going to go up and which are going to go down,
哪些股票将上涨 哪些将下跌
but you don't know by how much.
但是不知道上涨或下跌多少
You only know the sign of the change.
只是知道变化信号
So, in this case,
在这种情形下
the optimal portfolio is equal weight on all the stocks you take long positions on,
最佳投资组合是对所有做多的股票设定相同的权重
and equal weight on all the stocks you take short positions on.
并对所有做空的股票设定相同的权重
You can think of the regularization parameter as a dial that you can use to
你可以将正则化参数看做一个旋钮
tune between these two extreme versions of your prior knowledge of the world.
它可以在对世界的两种先验知识极端情形之间进行调节
This is the Bayesian interpretation of this technique.
这是这种技巧的贝叶斯解释
If you set the parameter equal to zero,
如果将参数设为零
that's the state where you have full confidence in the alpha vector.
对应的状态是你对 alpha 向量完全有信心
As the parameter approaches infinity,
当该参数接近无穷大时
the output weights approach equal weighting.
输出权重将接近同等加权
So, you can think of the regularization parameter as your conviction dial.
你可以将正则化参数看做信念调节旋钮